Kirishima-kun, it feels
like it's been ages.
Did you get a girlfriend or something?
You really wanna know?!
The truth is, there's this girl I like...
Wow, you're actually talking about
other girls at a time like this.
What's she like? Let me see a pic.
She's from Osaka.
This sucks... I can't
stand chicks like this.
Also, are these all candid pics?
You noticed?
Yeah, she won't let me take any pictures.
I get the feeling if I do anything too shady,
she's willing to die to take me down.
Sounds like she really hates you.
She's never actually said
that before, though.
Even if she's mad every single day.
Who's mad every day?
You should give it up.
Give it up? When I love her?
Do I really have to give up
on her when I'm in love?
She might even have a guy
in Osaka that she likes.
What if she's in a
long-distance relationship?
That sounds like it'd be
pretty hot in its own way.
You're so much of a freak, I'm
starting to pity this girl.
And I don't see why you're so
fixated on her in particular.
If she's mad all the time, that's too much.
The Triangle From Hell
Who's there... Grandpa?
No, I'm in Tokyo...
Tokyo?
It was just a dream.
No! That was definitely Kirishima.
I'm pretty sure I locked all the doors...
Did he pick the locks?
He'd have to actually cut the chain, though.
And what was he even after?
Is he bored enough of me
to try and kill me now?
Could be.
Damn it!
I've gotten so used to his shit by now
that it don't even bother me anymore!
This is getting ridiculous.
For now, I'll change the lock on the front
door, and for protection, I oughta...
Well, maybe not.
There he is!
Wh-What the hell is doing?!
And is that... blood?
If he's trying to kill me in
my sleep, he'll get closer.
Worst comes to worst, the
second he touches me...
H-He's braiding my hair?!
Enough's enough! I can't take it no more!
What in the hell are you—
Oh, you scared me. You were awake, Yoshino?
Y-Y-You're the one who scared me, dumbass!
Oh, sorry, that was kind of a reflex.
Seriously, sorry. I didn't hurt you, did I?
Put a sock in it!
What the hell were you doing?!
And how did you get in here?!
Well...
I used aluminum foil to make a replica key.
And some string took care of the chain...
You friggin' criminal!
Y'know what? Sit right there.
You're getting a lecture.
Okay.
I'm done trying to use abstracts like
crime and common sense with you.
Listen up. You don't open someone's room
without permission, much less waltz in.
Not just because it's common frickin'
sense, but because I do not like it!
Got it?
Got it.
Okay, next subject.
Why in the hell were you in my room, anyway?
Well?
I just realized, you always
look mad whenever I see you...
And someone pointed out
that maybe you hate me.
Which made me wanna see how you
look when you're sleeping...
I mean, no one's mad when
they're asleep, right?
Plus, that way I can look at you all I want.
Y'know...
Considering how pretty much everything
you do is on the wrong side of the law,
how am I supposed to look, other than mad?
You're even hurt, today.
Oh, this?
Tachibana-san let me have it
because I was out past curfew.
Curfew?! You've got a curfew?
Yeah, 1AM.
Not that I ever actually stick to it.
Are you trying to say you
don't want to make me mad?
I'm not sure how that's possible.
It's less that I don't
want to make you mad...
and more I wanna see you
when you're not mad?
Well, for starters, how about
you actually abide by that curfew?
You can't, can you? That's
what I'm getting at here.
Between how you won't stick
to simple rules
and how you've got other
girls all over you,
anyone would figure it out
after two or three weeks.
Girls?
You've got a mark on the back of your neck.
I'm surprised at how obvious
you can be sometimes.
The thing is, I'm pretty good
at picking up on that stuff.
Probably because my grandpa
gets around a lot.
If he had a kid with every one of his lovers,
my family tree'd be more complex
than a map of the city.
You don't have any kids running
around already, do you?
I think that... isn't an issue.
Well, get it together, lover boy!
What?
It's just... you noticed,
but you don't seem mad.
Why would I be mad?
Well... I was fooling
around with another girl.
And you're free to do so. I won't get mad.
That's really generous of you, Yoshino.
Naw, I'm a hothead.
If the guy I liked was fooling
around on me, I'd kill him.
What?
Well, if that's true, shouldn't
you want to kill me?
No, because I don't like you,
and I don't kill for fun.
Do you hate me, Yoshino?
Huh? Where's that coming from?
I've been enjoying every
day, with you around.
The thought of you being home
makes me want to rush back,
and having you with me even
makes school more fun.
Y'know, for such a brutal dude, you
sound like a grade schooler sometimes.
Do you hate me?
I don't avoid you because I hate you,
I do it because I never have any
idea what you're gonna do.
You refuse to do stuff you're uninterested in,
but when you do something, you go
all in. It's almost refreshing.
You don't put on airs.
You're always consistent.
If you've got any good points,
I'd say that covers them.
For now, I'm gonna put a bandage on,
and once that's done I want you out—
I love you too, Yoshino!
I'm gonna work hard so that when
I fool around, you'll wanna kill me!
What is your problem?!
It's hot... and I ended up
not gettin' enough sleep.
Good morning, Yoshino. You've
got a package from Osaka.
Hey, thanks. Is that for me too?
Nah, this is mine.
I sent a letter to Boss Somei,
so it's probably the response.
You wrote Grandpa?
It was a letter of apology.
Since I dragged you around the other
night and even got you hurt.
I called him too, of course.
You're weirdly considerate sometimes.
What'd you get?
What, this?
Just some photo album with my dad.
You'd be surprised by how normal he was.
Couldn't fight to save his life,
and he had a hate for yakuza that made him
butt heads with Grandpa all the time.
He moved out and got married as
soon as he graduated high school.
If I'm being honest, since he died
in an accident before I was born,
I don't have a strong sense of him.
An accident?
What now?
No, it's nothing.
Y'know, Boss Somei is coming to
Tokyo the day after tomorrow.
He didn't mention anything. What for?
There's an assembly for the Goyu-kai.
I appreciate you all for making
the time to join us tonight.
Especially Lieutenants
Somei Renji and Azuma Narumi
Kirigaya-gumi Lieutenant
Somei Renji
Azuma Narumi
of the Kirigaya-gumi who
have made quite the trip.
Himetorano Clan Chairman
Suga Ranzo
Tsuwabuki Clan Secretary General
Asebi Sho
Our agenda tonight, as the Kanto Goyu-kai,
Tsuwabuki Clan Chairman
Keyaki Katsuto
is to pool our wits beyond the
distinctions of east and west,
Tokusa Clan Acting Chairman
Miyama Gaku
so that we can contribute to the further
advancement of our organizations,
Tokusa Clan General Director
Akime Hishiba
both collective and individual.
Goyu-kai Chair
Katabami Clan Chairman
Ebine Reiji
Here's to collaboration.
The Kanto Goyu-kai is a sort of social
group for the yakuza groups in Kanto.
There's a dinner held four times a year,
and the heads of the
affiliated groups attend.
Think of it as a political summit.
Business doin' good?
You used to have to be a
group from Kanto to join,
The iron I bought the other
day has been really impressing me.
but now they've got the Kirigaya-gumi
from Kansai added to their number.
Really? Well, as far as we've been...
I had no idea at all.
And that's the way it should stay.
Don't go sticking your nose into it like you
did with the Akaza Enterprises business.
Y'know, when you mentioned your father,
it reminded me of something.
What the hell is this, Sota?
It tastes amazing.
Oh, we had some leftover okara,
so I made cookies out of it.
Here's an old picture of the boss.
What are you, a broad?
Don't make it again.
Boss Somei is in it, too.
But if you do, put some more sugar in.
Wait... is this Boss Miyama, then?
Yeah, that's him when he was younger.
Are you kidding me?!
He looks exactly like you!
You really think the
resemblance is that strong?
It's not a "resemblance"!
You literally are him!
Man, this picture makes the two
of them look pretty close.
They probably were actually good friends.
The boss hates photos, so these ten are the
only ones of him from when he was young.
And Boss Somei is in all ten of them.
Grandpa probably forced him to join in.
His own pictures were always
really shaky, though.
If you think about it, that
means they were close enough
that the boss didn't mind being
forced to take a picture.
That about covers it, yeah.
Were they close with this guy, too?
He's part of the picture.
Oh, that's Boss Akime from
the Ryuzetsu Family.
They go way back.
The Ryuzetsu Family are like us,
subordinates of the Tokusa Clan.
All three of them are heads
of major organizations now.
It's kind of amazing to think about
how they used to all pal around.
Gaku.
How've you been, lately?
Fine.
Man, you sound half-asleep!
You never did have a lotta pep in you, huh?
I'm not half-asleep. I've been
drinking, so I want to sleep.
You still can't hold your alcohol?!
I don't need to. I usually
choose not to drink.
Your poison was usually sweet
stuff instead of booze, right?
Got some candy for ya.
They were handing out
tissues by the station too,
and I got two so you can have—
Man, knock it off. I don't need
one, so don't stick it in my—
Renji. It's been a while.
Hey, Akishiba! It's been ages.
You're as rowdy as ever, I see.
That right?
Here, got a candy for you too.
Don't want it.
Boss, I've brought the car
around. We should go.
Let's get a move on, Gaku.
See ya.
Hey, Renji, there you are.
You ready to get some drinks?
Sounds good!
I was just thinking I
could go for a few more.
Let's get going, then.
An album?
Yeah. There oughta be another one
apart from the one they sent...
Where are you right now?
Over by my school.
Well, next time you're in Osaka,
could you check for it in my room?
Okay. I'll look for it.
Appreciate it.
Hotei-san! Good to see you.
Somei-gumi Member
Hotei Taketo
Hey, Yoshino. You been good?
Real good! Where's Grandpa?
Had his regular meeting at HQ,
so he went back to Osaka
without me last night.
You know how busy he is,
so try and forgive him.
You hungry? Wanna eat?
I'm good. I've got a lunch date later today.
With Boss Miyama's grandson?
Well, yeah...
What's he like?
You caused some trouble together
the other day, right?
Has he been dragging you around at night?
No, I wouldn't say that. But when
you ask me to describe him...
Masochist
Self-Destructive
Womanizer
Fake Smile
If I had to pick one thing, I'd
say he's really mentally durable.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, tell him you wanna drop by Osaka
during summer vacation to check in.
Why?!
Ain't that the sensible
thing to do in most cases?
I know this might sound obnoxious,
but I've been around you the most
since you were a baby, and I tend to
think I've taken the most care of you.
No, that's dead accurate.
You basically raised me, Hotei-san.
I barely remember seeing Grandpa
around when I was little.
Just... don't actually
tell him that, you hear?
Look, the thing is, I wanna see
if I can trust this kid to look after you.
But I don't wanna force it.
Nah, I think if I brought it up, he'd
probably wanna drop by as early as tomorrow.
Hello, it's nice
to meet you
I'm Miyama
Kirishima!
Shin-Osaka Station
Shin-Kobe
Kyoto
Hey, Shoma. You're finally here.
Sorry to bug you, Inamori-san...
The room that's locked over in
the separate storage building...
Should I clean it up?
That leads to the basement.
Even if you find it unlocked,
don't ever go down there.
The basement?
They apparently threw any members
who were addicted to drugs
down there to get sober.
Kirishima-san uses it now...
kinda weird that he does, honestly.
Sure, that's fine. It's been a while
since you've seen him, right?
Just let me know if you're going to be late.
I'll come pick you up.
Who travels overnight without
a change of clothes?!
I just came to drop this
off for you, Yoshino-san.
The album, right? Thanks! But you
are spending the night, right?!
Now get changed, already!
Did you head back to Osaka last night
and then come straight to Tokyo?
Yeah, that covers it.
You're as light on your feet as ever, huh?
I wanted to check on you, too.
There's no telling what you'll
do when you lose your temper.
I could say that right back to you!
You were still only 13 when
you joined up, right?
What kinda middle schooler
picks fights with yakuza?
I was drunk at the time.
Liar. I know it wasn't just booze.
You're lucky you picked
a fight with Grandpa.
Most of our guys are no good,
but if you had kept living the way you were,
you woulda ended up even worse off.
I guess you're right.
'Scuse me, miss? I'd like to buy this.
Put a damn shirt on!
Toriashi Shoma
...After the death of his mother, adopted
by his paternal grandparents.
...put into protective care for a time due
to conflict with grandparents.
...after dropping out of middle-school,
began living with his father.
...ostensibly adopted by the leader of
Somei-gumi, Somei Renji.
Toriashi Shoma.
You still eat a ton, huh?
And would you cover up a little more?
The whole idea is to get them
where people can't see, right?
Sorry.
I don't get why you and
Kirishima even bother.
What's he like?
Hotei-san asked me the same thing.
I didn't have a good answer.
Why not?
'Cuz I have no idea.
All I can say about the
guy is that he's crazy.
I'm probably better off not
treating him like a human being.
What the hell?
I've asked that, believe me.
And this dude is serious about
marrying you, Yoshino-san?
Sounds like it.
I dunno how serious to treat it, though.
And how do you feel?
Are you nuts? I ain't marrying that guy.
The idea is to get as much of his
attention as I can over the year,
dump him, and head home to Osaka.
Yoshino-san, do you know
how you ended up in Tokyo?
What do you mean? It was Grandpa
being crazy, wasn't it?
That's true, but...
Do you remember Suga Ranzo?
He's the chairman of the Himetorano Clan.
I know him. Grandpa and I took a trip with
Suga-san's family when I was little.
Do you know why he and the
boss are close, then?
Not really. They're friends, right?
Around the time the boss was my age,
the 4th chairman of the Kirgayama-gumi
and Himetorano Clan's chairman
became sworn brothers.
The Himetorano Clan is
pretty established in Kanto,
and that was how HQ started
gaining ground in Tokyo...
Kiriyama
Tokusa
Which ended up resultin' in a pretty
big fight with the Tokusa Clan.
But Grandpa and Boss Miyama
swore an oath last year, too.
Said the idea was to pursue
a more amicable route...
It might be the exact opposite.
When HQ and the Himetorano Clan
swore their oath, on the surface,
it was about making things more
peaceful between the east and west.
But...
There might be more fighting?
I dunno. The chance exists.
I think they've arranged to keep the boss
from making any aggressive moves
while you're in Tokyo, though.
Or maybe I'm overthinkin' it.
Forget I said anything.
I'm gonna get the tab.
Fighting, huh...
This sucks... I ate too much.
Whenever it's a buffet, I always try
too hard to get my money's worth...
I'm stuffed, I'm tired, and
I wanna just conk out.
You can take a nap if you want.
You're still good on time, right?
What time is it?
Past nine.
Nine already? I don't wanna go back.
I think somethin' about seeing you has
made me fed up with this whole deal.
What deal?
Wanting to beat Kirishima somehow, being
ready to kill him before he kills me...
Not showing any weakness, no matter what...
It's all I've been thinkin' about.
Did you lose your mind?
Shut it.
My point is, in spite of all that, he's
the only one I can turn to in Tokyo.
He's always fulla surprises.
Feels like no matter how
long we spend together,
I can never tell which face is his real one.
And it's exhausting!
Part of me wants to head home
with you to Osaka, right now.
Should we, then?
If this guy were gone, you wouldn't have
to worry like this, right, Yoshino-san?
I can kill him so you don't have to, then.
What the hell? That's a real escalation...
Well, from what you said, he
definitely sounds like bad news.
Maybe he's better off dead.
I'm no saint either, so killin' a
guy wouldn't be a big deal for me.
Now, hold on, it's not that bad yet.
I know. But when you're ready, let me know.
I'll be waitin'.
I'm gonna go smoke.
Part of me wants to head home
with you to Osaka, right now.
You're not allowed to smoke on
the street around here, buddy.
Nice to meet you, Toriashi Shoma-san.
I'm Miyama Kirishima.